# **Brandon Goff**

(630)488-1081

Brandonmgoff0@gmail.com / Brandonmgoff.com

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a highly organized and conscientious young professional currently working as an Office Support Specialist in the Housing department at NIU. I am also pursuing an undergraduate degree in OM&IS with the NIU college of business and use the skills cultivated in the classroom to achieve increasingly high levels of performance at work and vice versa. I have an affinity for working with large data sets, both commercial and consumer grade computer hardware, and enjoy being part of a team of passionate individuals motivated towards helping others succeed.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Northern Illinois University – DeKalb, IL: Housing Administration Representative SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

- I provide operational support across a wide variety of clerical and administrative tasks in both Grant Hall and the Northern View Apartment Community.
  - My responsibilities involve communication, coordination, and advocation for students and staff in matters regarding hall occupancy, record keeping, recruitment, relevant department purchasing, data entry, hall maintenance and servicing, and co-supervision of front desk student staff among other general clerical and administrative support tasks.
- The primary focuses of my role require generating robust and efficient independent methods of satisfying
  all university policies related to the responsibilities listed above while keeping processes flexible in
  anticipation of the ever-changing needs of our students and the department.
  - This has continued to encourage my development of high levels of organization and strong communication skills with internal and external entities.

# **Capital One - Rolling Meadows, IL:** *Sr. Customer Service Representative* JUNE 2015 - JUNE 2017

• I served in the partnership credit division specializing in retail accounts.

- This role provided service to 60+ vendor partners.
- I have serviced credit accounts in excess of \$500,000.
- I have experience and proficiency in multiple database platforms including DOS format.
- I became highly proficient in Outlook scheduling and internal corporate communication.
- I consulted in providing feedback for a diverse range of internal process improvements.
- Part of my responsibilities included providing basic tech support to customer accounts.

## **Pinstripes - South Barrington, IL:** *Corporate Trainer*

AUGUST 2014 - DECEMBER 2018

- I traveled to Cleveland and helped in opening the company's 10th location.
  - This was to assist in training local hires during the locations grand opening event and involved managing service teams for hosting events including large corporate events and weddings.
  - I am one of only 2 service trainers in the company to have been sent back to the location and provide staff training an additional two times.
  - I was the only member of the organization to have serviced the two largest events in company history at the time, the largest generating revenue of \$165,000.
- This role requires extremely precise time management and high levels of Organization.
- I am capable of high levels of physical stamina in a high energy work environment.

#### **SKILLS**

**<u>High level customer service</u>**: Leading service teams for 500+ person events, basic tech support, servicing credit accounts, coordinating campus-wide booking changes, scheduling internal events across university departments, etc.

**Extremely adept with technology**: Maintaining multiple databases simultaneously, Basic hardware/software troubleshooting, Proficient across Microsoft office applications (Excel, Access, Outlook, Word, Teams, PowerPoint etc.).

**Leadership:** Co-supervisor of residence hall front desk student staff performance and recruitment.

### **EDUCATION**

Northern Illinois University - DeKalb, IL: Bachelor's Degree: OM&IS (In progress)
JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

- Operations Management/Information Systems (OM&IS)
- Familiar with Agile management frameworks
- Leadership Training
- 3.49 GPA (as of Fall 2023 semester)